I'm with Landscape Restorations in Miami, Florida.
We're here at Palm Hammock Orchid Estate and we're talking about planting, and fertilizing.
The title of this clip is trees and puppies grow up.
Just like giraffes and tiger cubs and puppies and kittens, trees grow up.
Here's a good example of the wrong plant in the wrong place.
We have a wood planter box here filled with beautiful begonias and crotans and geraniums, and then we have a little problem right here.
Here's royal palm that looked good when it went in as a pot, but tree is going to grow up to be a street size tree.
This will be easily 50 or 60 feet tall.
It will demolish this planter box.
It will get too big for the location and it will eventually get to be a real hazard, especially in a wind storm.
Here in Miami we have hurricanes, tornadoes and other things.
Wrong plant; wrong place.
Beware of what happens when the trees grow up.
This will also drop palm fronds right into a parking lot right into a drive way.
Be careful.